{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_3LQPL9",
                "player_6_3LQPL9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -848.452,
                    -616.765,
                    207.853,
                    0,
                    -92.41766280915425,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -654.444,
                    -918.097,
                    206.314,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_3LQPL9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -601.923,
                    -762.931,
                    408.74,
                    0,
                    -37.93608161145437,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "animal": {
            "name": [
                "animal_10_3LQPL9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                10
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Large Komodo dragon with rugged scales, powerful limbs, and a long tail"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -1068.75,
                    -1056.135,
                    204.264,
                    0,
                    162.82982553506633,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -977.414,
            -938.385,
            206.465
        ],
        "sample_radius": 614.4668537072657
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone",
        "animal"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            63.268,
            -754.908,
            201.898,
            0,
            -174.4279750980043,
            0
        ],
        [
            -1200.33,
            -675.088,
            201.897,
            0,
            -21.876490339134925,
            0
        ],
        [
            -396.005,
            -1284.18,
            241.818,
            0,
            131.72040472308223,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_black_vest or Komodo_Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. Komodo_Dragon"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, White_Drone or Komodo_Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. Komodo_Dragon"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_woman_in_black_vest or Komodo_Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. Komodo_Dragon"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_man_in_blue_polo or Komodo_Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. Komodo_Dragon"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to Komodo_Dragon, the_woman_in_black_vest or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to Komodo_Dragon, the_man_in_blue_polo or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are observed in a standing posture in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many distinct male individuals are present among the people?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many entities are equipped for aerial operation in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are holding something?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many reptiles are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. resting",
                    "D. saluting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the Komodo Dragon relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the Komodo Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the Komodo Dragon relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the front of",
                    "C. To the back of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the Komodo Dragon?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Above and to the front-left of",
                    "B. Below and behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Above and to the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Below and in front of",
                    "B. Above and behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the front-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Above and behind"
            }
        }
    }
}